(Raj:)I bet you told Bernadette
all about he was screwing around
with Mandy Chao.
(Leonard:)Oh, we didn't screw around.
(Leonard:)We just got drunk and made out.
(Raj:)Whatever. It would have
been nice to hear it from you.
(Amy:)What are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)I'm here to return
your belongings.
(Sheldon:)That's what people
who've broken up do.
(Amy:)And you didn't do
your compulsive knocking ritual
(Amy:)so I would open the door.
(Sheldon:)On the contrary,
(Sheldon:)you no longer get to enjoy
my charming eccentricities.
(Sheldon:)We're not friends with benefits.
(Amy:)Just give me the box.
W-Wait. Don't you want
to go through it
(Sheldon:)to make sure
I haven't forgotten anything?
(Amy:)Fine.
(Amy:)My old scarf.
(Sheldon:)You wore it the night
we went ice-skating. Remember?
(Amy:)You mean the night
that I went ice-skating,